Sabse [Music]
Gana Mana Adhinayak
Jai Hey Bharat Bhagya Vidhata Watan Van
Mera [Music] Rahe Guru Main Jahan Rahun Jahan Me Lal
[Music] Rahe Tu Desh
Rangeela Rangeela Desh Mera Rangeela
So Hello Guys Welcome To A New Blog.  So
guys, today's blog is going to be very
special because guys, today is our 15th August
program for which
preparations are going on in full swing.  And guys, today it has been
79 years since India got independence.
And today the 80th Independence
Day is being celebrated with great pomp in India.
So Happy Independence Day to you from me and my entire family.
Guys, the
decoration was completed yesterday and today the
remaining preparations are being done.
So let me show you
how the preparations are going for today.  So
look guys, the stage is getting ready here.  So it will
feel very nice.  At present the
preparations are going on.  Prachi has come after taking bath.
Prachi's dance practice is
complete and final.
Yes,
you have done it completely Vanshu.
How to do it?
I have a side role, I will stay behind.   Yes, he does
n't know.
I will keep looking at you like this.
Come on Vanshu, let's show you the outside decoration now.   Come on.
So let me show you guys again
how the decoration has been done.
So Ton Tan Guys let's start here.
Hello Bhaiya [laughs]
Yes guys, look, Bhaiya has
put up tricolour flags all around which
look very beautiful.  And guys, let me
show you our dhaba also.  Look
guys, brother has decorated our dhaba also.  And
look guys, this tree has also been decorated by Bhaiya.
And here some such decoration has been done.
So look here, wow, it looks so beautiful,
right?  Meaning, there is tricolour everywhere.
Aunty, Happy
Independence Day.
Yes, everyone too.
So look guys, our aunt has
worn tricolour bangles.  Aunt had worn it last night itself.
Aunt, we have a program today.
Today I am finishing my work quickly.
Yes, do it quickly.   We will do an
afternoon program.  We will see and
aunty, sit down and
listen, you also have to sing a nice song on the stage
which you had sung.   The
voice is low.
Oh, it's okay, Aunty.  Today is such a special day for
us.
Today I will feel even more embarrassed.
No.  [laughs]
Guys, our aunt and mother,
we are also coming home.
Yes, aunt and mother are very shy.   Meet me
inside.
Yes aunty, I will introduce you.  Some special
guests have also come to our house.  Aunty, tell me
how is the decoration looking?
very nice.
Looking very beautiful, isn't it?  Meaning,
people passing by in Guys Gali are asking.  Hey, is
anyone coming here?
Yes, I am saying that there is some big function.
Someone is coming from far away like this.
Hey, everyone is asking whether any leader is coming
?  [laughs] It
all
looks really beautiful.
And today some guests have also come to our house, for
whom you all were waiting, but no
one came from your sister-in-law's house.  So today their
mom and dad have come from Sanju's sister-in-law's house.
Yes, taking brother's stuff.
What mom?
Brought the stuff for Teej.  Bhabhi's gift has come from Bhabhi's house.
Yes.  So look guys, today
some special guests have come to our house.  Guys Bhabhi
's mom, dad and younger brother have come.  So let
me introduce you guys.  Papa ji
Radhe-Radhe.
And how are you, Papa?
Mummy ji Radhe-Radhe.
How are you?
very nice.  We were very happy to see you.   I liked it
very much
and our sister-in-law will be very happy.
So brother, he will be happy that his parents have come.
When parents come to pick up or
meet their daughter, there is a feeling of happiness from within.  Meaning
our mom and dad are coming or our
period is coming to take us at any age.   It feels
so happy inside [laughs].
And our brother is getting sad.  They are saying,
Jyoti ji, please don't go.
We take along [laughs] for two days.
[Sudden sound of heavy breathing]
Guys, today Bhabhi's parents have come to our house to
pick her up.  So today our sister-in-law will go
back to her home with you.   Will I have to come
again with the wedding procession
?  [laughs] If you do
n't bring a wedding procession, I'm coming simply anyway.
[suddenly loud breathing]
So come on mom, have some tea.
And guys, meet them.  This is our sister-in-law's
youngest brother.  Hi.
Hi.
How are you?  You came by train, right?  So
what time did you sit in the morning?
7:00 pm.
Sat at 7:00 in the morning.
So you like travelling by train
?
Sounds great.  So let's go, this is our
program today.  You should also see that before leaving.
And look guys, the stage has been set.
Brother will do the decoration on the stage now.
And here Bhaiya Vanshu are
building the river together.  Guys, see
how much preparation is required before the program.
That too to us only.  We are the ones doing it.
We have also set up the stage.  We will do the rest of the
preparations as well.  So brother,
preparations are going on right now.  Right now I also have to go get
ready.
Brother, the
stage has been set.
Who will do the rest of the decoration?  So very normal basic preparation has been done.
So the main preparations are like the preparation of the chandelier,
putting up the decoration stuff, yes that is true, so
brother you will do all that,
yes all that, oh
brother brother is sweating so much,
see, there is
this advantage in doing it yourself, we can do it as we
wish,
yes, it will happen as we wish, if we
tell someone, the tent guy, he will do his
work and go away,
well guys, the same preparations are going on here, the
decoration of the stage is still left, there is still a
lot of work left,
right now Lal, I have to go to the flat.  I have received a
call from Didi two-three times saying that you should also
come, you should also get ready.  Sometimes I might find out that our
program starts and I am not ready and
on time.  So come on brother, should I go get
ready?  So come on guys, I will quickly get
ready and come.  I feel that by the time
I come here, all the stages
etc. will be completed.  So let's go to the
flat now.  So guys, I have just
reached my flat to my sister
and bhabhi because guys, now we have to get
ready, so look guys, our didi did her
make-up early in the morning, took a
bath early in the morning, she is not telling
[laughs] she did her
make-up, she is telling
good morning didi, by the time she woke up,
we had cooked the food, swept and mopped it,
then madam woke up, gave her tea, madam said the
tea was very sweet
[laughs]
and bhabhi
good morning.
Good Morning.
How are you sister-in-law?
Excellent.   Have you finished your
dance practice?
Yes it is done.
Excellent.  Today we have to perform very well.
Yes.   Isn't it
?   I will
dance.
Yes.  And sister-in-law, what have you cooked for dinner today
?  Show me once.
Our audience will have some mouth watering.   Same oy hoye.
Our sister has made cabbage, potato and this matar paneer.
Oh wow.  So brother, didi has made matar paneer
sabji and rice along with it and
get comfortable and have made poorma hot poo rice and here
didi has made hot raita ready [laughs].
Hot
Bhabhi, our sarees have arrived.  Yes, I will
ask sister, sister, when will we be
ready brother?
I have got a grandson.  I applied POP.
Brother, please get me ready too, sister.  So come on guys, let
us all get ready quickly.
Brother, I have to get ready and reach the
other house quickly because I have to show
you all the preparations going on there.  Is
n't it sister?  So get
me ready quickly too.  I will go then.
So finally guys we are all ready.   And
guys, our 15th August program is going to start in a short while.
Look guys, our stage is also ready.
Come on guys,
look at this, but brother,
how will we get on the stage?  You didn't even make it to climb.
Yes,
sorry, we forgot.   Will you
climb like this?  Let us
make all of them right now.  Stop, grab the camera.
Hey, how is it Bhaiya, it will be ready now
Bhaiya,
friend, how is the director sahab, our Bhabhi,
show us there, you do half the work, I did
n't know that you are in a corner, do
n't come to the corner, look [laughs]
Hey Bhaiya, you know what you are going to do, we will
bend here, we will put the carpet on Bhaiya,
come on, come on, put your
feet and
climb Bhabhi, it
seems Bhaiya has seen Bahubali a lot, has
seen Bahubali a bit too much [laughter]
Madam, climb, oh oh oh
Bhaiya Bhabhi will climb, how will we
climb [laughter]
Devsena,
oh my god,
this is
right,
guys Bhabhi has climbed, but how will we climb
on the climb,
brother, your promise is a bit too much [laughter], even her
husband has not come
[laughter]
wait, it's your time, it's your
time,
hey,
we have climbed, take care of yourselves, it's okay, guys,
look
Keshav guys, the
stage looks very nice, the
decoration of the stage has been done very well,
look at that, brother, the dance
practice is still going on here.  Move aside, I will
make it for you.
Hey brother, you are making it at the last moment.  Hey, I was
saying it calmly and tell me on the spot that the
stairs are being built.  And guys, look,
today all three of us, me, sister-in-law and sister, are
wearing sarees of the same colour.  So we are looking very good, are
n't we?  Guys, if you
like it then please give it a like.
Like it.
And guys, today our Aadu is also
wearing a white frock.  Addu even
danced once.  He danced very well.   Let's
ask the rest from aunt.  Aunty, how do we three
look?   You are
looking very good.
Brother, we have a group dance.  We should look good,
right?   The
dress should be the same.
Yes.
We are different from the rest.  All three of us are the same.
Rest look guys, all the preparations are done here
brother.  The stage has been set up,
decoration has been done and
chairs have also been placed here.  But there is a problem,
guys.  Look, it is raining.   I
hope our program doesn't get cancelled.
Prachi had also come.
Yes sister, I am afraid the program might get cancelled.   Is it
right sister-in-law?  Look at us how we are
sweeping.  They are laying the string.
You came prepared.
What a dress with the flag.
Now it's all over myself.  So go and get ready.
Wear something, just wear orange.  Add orange.
Wear something, friend.
Wear a white shirt.
I will wear green and white.  green White.   There
is also orange.   Just
look at this uncle.  Uncle,
you should also wear a white shirt.
Son, we are watching everything.  Now if we
wear white, we will get dirty.
Yes.
Even uncle's white clothes will turn black.   That's why I am
saying that I am not wearing it.
Look, I have even
worn bangles with the tricolour.
So you didn't do any work, did you?
Yes.   Be
ready.  Papa has come.
Yes guys, look, today our father is also
looking very handsome.  [laughs]
Dude,
our dad looks really good today.
So brother,
our 15th August program is going to
start in a short while.  Just a
few people are coming.  We are waiting for him only.
Like our Kajal didi is also coming now.
Is it sister-in-law?  Yes.
And our guys stage is looking very nice.  Guys,
we are going to dance on this stage.
Rest of the decoration is wow guys, if you
liked the decoration then
please give it a like.  And guys, let me introduce you to this one too.
Hello guys this is
Bhumi.  And Bhumi is also going to dance.  Bhumi,
on which song will you dance?
We can understand people.  Wow, you did
practice the dance, right?  So let's go, that's a very
good thing.  You want to give a good dance
performance, right?  And look guys,
our Aadu, brother Aadu comes on stage again and again.
Addu come here.
Hey wow Adu, which song are you going to dance to
?
Those with the tricolour.
Still my heart is Indian.  Say.   On that
song.
Which one?
On the tricolor song.  The audience was very fond of singing the tricolour song,
O Bhai
Bhai, burn the DJ Wale Babu song.
[laughs] I am
running it son, I will run the satsang.
Bhabhi, I am feeling very excited.   It is
happening but it is also confusing
that our step might be something else.
Because brother has set up such a big stage
and everyone will see us.
Stage.
Yes.
And look guys, everyone is sitting here.
So let me introduce you guys to everyone [music].
So our elder
mother and mother are sitting here and look guys, mother is
wearing an orange colored saree.  Mom, you are
looking very beautiful.   You are
wearing an orange colored saree, right?
Yes.  And mom, please don't support us.
If we forget our dance after going on stage, then keep
telling us the steps from behind.
Ok.
Okay mom, you too.
And look guys, Nani is sitting here.
Nani, will you support us?
And guys, our director sir is also ready.
Brother, are you ready?
Yes, I am ready friend.  My clothes remained at home.
Oh
wear this and dance.
Brother, someone please wear an orange colored T-shirt.
[Music]
Hey, that's it,
hey, there's no one, man.
I feel that brother is tired.  Is
n't it brother?   So I have finished
dancing but now I will have to go home.
Yes, that is true.  And look guys, our
mother has also come to see our program.
So let's make Amma sit on the seat too.  Come on
Amma.  So Nani and Amma will
sit together.
So come on brother, mother has also come.
And aunty, are you ready?
Yes
brother, it looks very nice.  Isn't it?
And Guys happiness has also arrived.  Hello Khushi.
Brother, are you ready to dance?  Which
song are you dancing to?
Friend, I forgot to remember.   I
forgot to sing the song O Bhai and Mauka Pe.
Then how will the dance happen?  I am feeling scared here
brother.  We are also feeling scared.
What should I give?
I danced very well.   Yes,
you danced very well.  Look guys, the
big flag here is getting
ready.
Where will they plant the dynasty and where will they plant it on
this?   Why do
n't you ask your brother where to put this?   It will be here.   It will be here.
Oh wow, that would be great.
So let's start with Adu.  Otherwise, if the
rain becomes heavy.   Yes, yes.
So guys let's start the program
with our cute Addu.
Guys, now our special program of 15th August
is starting and we will start with
our lovely Adu.  So now
Addu will dance.  So let's get started now guys.
So let's go, Adu.
Let's go one two three.
[Music]
This is my [song voice] India
this is my India I
love my India
well it's over everyone give a big round
of applause very good
[screaming voice]
because of Vinayak no,
Vinayak has come no, she got distracted
yes yes her brother has come distracted
[laughter] she got distracted.
No problem, Altu has performed very well.
And guys, our Kajal didi has also come.
Hello, how are you?
Excellent.  Tell me how are you?
Well done, you have come at the right time.
Our program has just started.
See, I came at the right time.
Yes.  And you look great today.
I have also come wearing a green and white saree.
Yes.  So as we are getting late for the program,
so keeping the time in mind we should
move towards our next performance and the next performance is going to be done by
Bhoomi
[screaming voice]
who studies in fourth class Bhoomi are you
ready
then let's go Bhoomi is ready so the song should be played
and first of all a big round of applause should be given to Bhoomi let
's play the song
[music]
Hoti [song voice] is
this [screaming voice]
very good a big round of applause for Bhoomi
Bhoomi has done a very good dance performance
just now and now next
Bade Papa is going to give a speech and is
looking for her for his speech.
[laughter]
Bade Baba sang
Bade Baba come.
Wherever Bade Papa is, please come on stage.
Papa has gone to prepare a speech.  Brother,
when will elder father come?  [laughter]
Mom.
Yes.
How did you like the performance of our Bhoomi and Addu?
very good.
Excellent.
How did you like mom?   I liked it
very much.
And guys, look everyone has come here.  So
how did you like Bhumi's performance?   I liked it.
How did you like it?
And we really enjoyed it.  You
came to see our program.  So enjoy this special program of ours like this.   Did you
like it, Aunt?
Yes, I liked it very much.
Now its your turn.
No, it's not my turn.  Your turn will
come.  What
song now
?
Now aunt will sing.
Which song will you sing brother?
Of.  Oh brother oh brother our Bade Papa has come,
we heartily welcome Bade Papa
with clapping,
so welcome Papa with hearty applause
[laughs] so
come on come up and let's
see guys our Bade Papa will
give a speech cute guys now our Bade Papa will
give a speech so let's start
heartiest wishes to all of you on Equality Day,
today after 80 years our India has progressed a lot.
Science, technology, education.  But
I believe that India's best
future is yet to come.  Today we have
only this to say to our children and youth.  Keep your dreams
big.  Work hard honestly and
let's say from the whole side.  Long live Mother India.
Vande
Mataram.
very nice.  [Praise]
So Baba has given a very good speech.   A big round of
applause for them, once again, very
good.  And now let's move towards our next performance
which Prachi is going to give, she has
prepared this performance with a lot of hard work.
Come Prachi ji, come, you are absolutely welcome.
Big applause for Prachi ji.  very
nice.  Come on
[Music]
Give a big round of applause Give a big round of applause
Give a big round of applause Give a big round of
applause to the good performance of
Priya ji Very good very
good
and Prachi worked very hard
for this performance Prachi has given a very good performance
and now we are leaving our last
performance of today is ours which has been
prepared by the entire team of Family Wives
So it is raining I would like the
team of Family Wives to come on stage quickly guys
now it is our turn so now we will dance
Rama Hare Rama Rama Rama Hare Hare Krishna Hare Krishna Krishna Krishna Hare
[Music]
London Mein [Music] Dekha Ja Ye
Duniya Ek Dulhan [Music] Dulhan Ke
Maathe Ki
Duniya [Music] Jitna Bhi Samjhoge Utni Hogi
[Song voice] Hairaan
[Music] Hai
Hindustan
Mein [Song voice] Haathon Mein Ho
[Music]
Aaja Aaja
Ke
Aasmane [Music]
India [Music] [
Music]
[Music]
So guys our performance is over and
now the last one will be Jana Gana.  so let's start.
Janagan [Music] Mana Adhinayak
[Song voice]
Jai he Bharat Bhagya Vidhata
Jai ​​[Music] [Song voice] Jai Jai he
Bharat Mata ki Jai
Bharat Mata ki Jai Vande
Mataram Vande
Mataram
[Music] I am yours wherever I am, I
remember you
[Music]
Desh Rangila Rangila Desh [Music] Mera
Rangila Desh Rangila Rangila Desh Mera Rangila
So guys, our 15th August
program is over today.  And guys, if
you liked our program today, then
please give it a like.  Now it is
time for our sister-in-law and her parents to go back to their home.   There
is a train at 5:00.  So mom
brought the festival of Teej for mom and aunt.
So let's give it a go now.  [Music]
Guys, now our Bhabhi is going back to her home
and now I don't know when I will get to meet her.
Only one hour is left.  If
mom, dad and sister-in-law do
not reach the railway station before 1 hour, they will miss the train today.  So that's why
everything is happening in a hurry.
So come on mom, bye.
Bye
hello mom.
hello.   Ok
Bye.
[Music]
No one
Look guys, our sister-in-law
is ready and is now going back home.   That means
guys Bhabhi is going to Moradabad.
So come on sister-in-law, bye.   Bye.   Take
care of yourself
Yes.
And come quickly.  We won't feel like it.
Good sir.   Guys, it's
not that we do
n't want to send our sister-in-law.   The
only thing is that we will not feel like it.   Is
n't it sister-in-law?
So let's meet soon sister-in-law.   It is
after Rakhi, right?
So let's meet you all now.
Bhai, everything, so much hurry,
why is Chachi making us, we used to drink tea everyday, I
missed you a lot [laughs]
[laughs]
and Lalli come [laughs] I will be alone.
This is our Lalli, I am their Lalli.  [laughter]
Why would you be alone?  It won't be long, we will
meet again on Rakshabandhan.
Yes,
come back soon after enjoying well.
Now she will also grow up in the live.
This little Lalli is
fine.
Hey friend, let's meet her
[laughs] [sudden sound of heavy breathing]
Prachi,
come on guys, now Bhabhi is going to her house and now
we will go again, she is going with the wedding procession.
Yes [laughs] that's right, Bhaiya is crying.   Will have to do it.
Brother, don't
cry for your brother, take the wedding procession,
our brother is crying.   I will get
ready.  Ok.
What am I saying sister-in-law, please bring the
wedding procession.  Don't cry
[laughs]
Bhaiya, you will have to become a groom again.   Come on.
Okay brother, after Rakshabandhan and brother is saying that
I will bring it on 20th because
he will not be in the mood.
No guys,
our brother is going to leave sister-in-law.
Then we will dance after leaving.  My
wife went to her parents' house.  [laughter]
Brother, he'll dance.
Yes I know.  They feel happy.
Look, tea is being distributed to celebrate your departure.   She has gone.
I am organizing a tea distribution.
Look at it.   That's
ok.  Bye.  The train will be missed.
Come on, come on, bye.  Yes, hello guys,
today everyone is in such a hurry that we are not even
realizing it, so
I am leaving, okay Bhabhi
[Sangeet] I want to
eat, Vinayak, Vinayak, come on,
Bhabhi, it is not like that you will miss the train,
we are sending you quickly, you will miss the train, come on, come on,
brother, our children's aunt has come, she will
give us money to eat cheese,
brother, I am also Choti Nand,
now you stand up.
Good sir.   They
are nephews and nieces, right
Babu?  Ok.  Eating lots of that chocolate.
Ok.
[Music]
Come on, Papa, hello.
hello.
Come on brother, now we are going to drop Bhabhi outside.
Bye Bhabhi.
Okay sister-in-law, bye.
Bye mom.   Bye.   Bye.
And look guys,
some of our subscribers
also came to watch our 15th August program today and are sitting with us today.
So come on guys, let me introduce you guys.
Hello brother.
Hello
Namaste.
hello.
How are you?
Ok.
And how did you like our program today?   Adored.
And how did you like our dance?   I
liked your dance too.  But we were
late in coming due to rain.
But I saw that you had come while we were dancing.
Yes, I had arrived by that time.
But today, because of the rain, everything happened a little
quickly.   It
rained.
And guys, meet them.  This is brother's wife.
Hi.
hello.
How are you?  It's very nice.
How did you like our program today?   I liked it.
We just came last.   Do
n't look.
We did not try to do better.
But everything got spoiled because of the rain.   That's
correct.
Yes.
And guys, get it.  This is our little
cute subscriber.
Tell me your name.  Nice name.
Okay, tell me your name.
What is your name?
Nitya.
What is the name?
Nitya.  Oh wow.  Hello
[laughs]
and meet the guys.  Hello
hi
how are you?
Sir, how are you?
Excellent.  You have come very late.
Too late.  It happened because of the rain.
I saw that our program was over
when I saw you.
Yes.
By the way, where do you come from?
I am from Ramnagar.
So, where did you get our address?   I
just met my relatives who lived there.
Well, that's a very good thing.
Got dressed.  And guys, meet them.  Hello Aunty ji.
Hi
hello.
Hello son.
How are you?
Okay, you tell me.
Excellent.
And how did you feel meeting all of us?
Very good.  Very good.  There should be such a family.
My family is also like this.
Good.   It is a
very nice family.  I really
enjoyed meeting you and your family.  We
check out all your blogs.  It
feels very nice.  It doesn't feel like we are
looking at someone else or at someone else.  It
seems as if our own people are watching.   The
mind also gets refreshed after reading the blog.
Does
n't your mind get refreshed after reading the blog?
Well, but we normally make blogs about home.   I
mean, you like the family, right? What does that mean?   I really like
your blog.  Whatever you
make, it looks very nice.  The
best video I found was the one made by your sister-in-
law.  She came disguised as an Englishwoman and took away the
loot [laughs].  I liked her very much.   It seemed so.  I was
laughing a lot at the
video,
Kajal didi's dance,
Kajal didi's dance is awesome, last last,
not awesome, while dancing in a wedding [laughs] they do
comedy, right? Yes, it looks good,
Shilpa is
awesome, absolutely
great, when she was coming with
her brother,
her hair was like this [laughs] they said she has fallen ill,
yes, brother scolded me a lot,
what if I did not get the witch look to do it once,
brother scolded me many times in that.
I was not laughing at that time.  [laughter]
Oh, the one who was taking out the Shimla slip.   Guys,
today we were very happy that
some of our subscribers came to meet us and
also came to watch our program.
We enjoyed it very much.
We have seen each and every one of your vlogs.  Each one is
good.  First of all we saw Vaishno Devi.   There are a
lot of updates now.
What?
Now let's update the vlog.  [laughter]
Let's see the update.
And guys now our subscribers are also going back to their
homes.  Okay, bye bye brother.
Like bye bye bye karo bye [laughs]
brother, this is exactly like our Aadu.
Radhedhe Radhedhe
Radhedhe
Yes, he doesn't know how to say Radhedhe like Radhika.   I do
n't know how to say ok
Radhe Radhe
[laughs]
[sudden sound of heavy breathing]
Bye Nitya bye
and guys now aunty ji is also going back to her home.
ok aunty ji hello bye bye
I did not even ask your name now my
name is Jyoti
Jyoti oh wow Jyoti is our sister in law's
name too same same same
yes mummy
same name
yes
and Sanju is my niece's name
ok [laughs]
bye
how did you like meeting us I want to meet
Sanju didi
how did you like meeting us
when will you come to meet me again
chappals will you
come soon come on bye so guys it is
7:00 in the evening now and
guys now Sonu bhaiya and Anshu are going to
Shilpa didi's house to celebrate Teej
because guys tomorrow is Teej and we have
celebrated Independence Day today now tomorrow
we will celebrate Teej
tomorrow we will celebrate Teej festival
yes Teej celebration so a day before Teej
bhaiya and Anshu are going to didi's house to celebrate Teej
festival.  So come on brother, I am quite late today
because we had a function today,
yes, but I have to go anyway, so go at
this time, go
quickly, come back home
quickly,
Aunty, why should we let these boys go today, today these boys are in
trouble,
today they are working because of this, the
poor guys have been working since yesterday morning, they are doing
well and now we have sent them there, come on,
yes sister's house is so far, no
one will come and rest at night,
yes, that's it, the
boys get their sleep,
Aunty, I am feeling very tired today,
I too have woken up very early in the morning.
And see, tomorrow also there will be Teej celebration.   Come
early tomorrow too.
Oh ho, look at aunty's earrings, guys,
aunty is wearing exactly matching earrings.
Hum, this is the jhumka song, right?  [laughs]
Looks good.
Yes, they look good.  Guys, today we
celebrated Independence Day.  Rest guys,
tomorrow is Teej festival.  Tomorrow is Independence Day as well as
Teej.  So now we will prepare for the
Teej festival.  So look guys,
sister has applied mehndi on her brother.
Brother, I was busy working.  Look at this.
Who is speaking and taking the name of work.
Brother, only those who are able to save money from work apply mehndi.
I don't have any work, I have gone to keep my stuff.  I
looked up and saw her making a video
like this.
[laughs]
So guys, now we will celebrate Teej tomorrow.
So a lot of preparations have to be done for that too.  So
brother, will you set up a swing for us tomorrow?
Yes brother, preparations will begin.
This swing will be installed tomorrow.  Tomorrow we will all swing.
I will also apply my mehndi the rest of the night.
So, I am feeling very tired right now.   Is
n't it sister?  We are very tired
today.  Pain in the legs
and Vanshu had just fallen
asleep during the day.  This function went to
sleep only after our program was over.  So come on guys, this
celebration will happen tomorrow.
So with this let's end this blog here.
I hope you liked today's blog.  If you
like it then like it.  Do
subscribe to our channel Family Vibes.
See you in the next blog.  Thank you for
watching.  Bye.